

Luis Gerardo Gomez Romero

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- gerardogomezromero175@gmai l.com
- +526646325891
- ▼ Tijuana, Mexico

MY LINKS

- GeraOSF
- in geraosf
- @ geraosf.github.io
- mnf.red/gerardogomez

Introduction

I'm Gerardo Gomez, a Front-end Web Developer with experience developing software solutions in the current company I'm working in, but also doing projects for clients as a freelancer.

My skills



Adaptability to change



Proactivity



Team player

Technologies and tools

I MASTER

React / JavaScript / HTML / CSS / Python / C / SQL / TypeScript / Jest / Tailwind

Languages

Spanish

NATIVE/BILINGUAL

English

FLUID

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE/CAREER

THIRDROCK SYSTEMS

ThirdRock Systems

Frontend Web Developer
 Oct 2022 — TODAY

Working with a team as a frontend web developer for the Canadian company ThirdRock Systems.

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

JavaScript / HTML / CSS / WordPress



Upwork

Freelance Web Developer

Sep 2022 — TODAY (1 month)

Developing software solutions for clients all around the world in the freelance site Upwork.

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

JavaScript / React / HTML / CSS / TypeScript / Jest / Tailwind



LYPSA

Electronic diagnostic and repair technician

Sep 2020 — Feb 2021 (5 months)

Diagnose and repair faulty circuits from a telecommunications company called Izzi



Voxcentrix

Bilingual Customer Service Representative

Jun 2018 — Aug 2018 (2 months)

Car insurance agents for clients in the United States.

EDUCATION/**DEGREES**

Degrees



Instituto Tecnológico de Tijuana

Electrical Engineer

Aug 2015 — TODAY (7 yrs. and 2 months)

Currently at my last semester in Electrical engineer specializing in automation.

TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

Python / C / C++ / Matlab

Courses & Self Training

Oracle Next Education - Full stack development, Alura Latam
 Apr 2022 — TODAY (6 months)

Learn React, ScrimbaJul 2022 — Aug 2022 (1 month)

— CS50: Introduction to Computer Science, Harvard University
 Jan 2022 — May 2022 (4 months)

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures, FreeCodeCamp Nov 2021 — Feb 2022 (3 months)

Certificates



JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification

Issued by: FreeCodeCamp
Feb 2022 — TODAY (8 months)



Mechanical Design at the level of Associate

Issued by: Dassault Systèmes

May 2021 — TODAY (1 year and 5 months)



e-Series Core Track - Robotic Arm Programming

Issued by: Universal Robots A/S Oct 2020 — TODAY (2 yrs.)



BUT WAIT... THERE'S EVEN MORE IN MY PROFILE.

This is a short version of my Profile, but a longer one is available where you can see more interesting and relevant data.



+ Click here or scan the QR code